<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TechnoRange</string>

    <string name="onboard_heading_one">Welcome to TechnoRange!</string>
    <string name="onboard_heading_two">Find What You Need</string>
    <string name="onboard_heading_three">Easy and Safe Checkout</string>

    <string name="onboard_descript_one">Your Online Marketplace for all Tech Needs and Online Seller Hub for all Tech Trades.
        Explore a world of computer peripherals, where trading meets convenience. Discover, connect, and trade seamlessly.
        Let\'s get started on your tech journey! </string>
    <string name="onboard_descript_two">Dive into our extensive range of computer parts with ease. Use the search bar to find
        specific items or refine your search with our intuitive filters. Your perfect computer upgrade is just a click away. </string>
    <string name="onboard_descript_three">Ready to make your purchase? Enjoy a hassle-free checkout experience. Enter your billing details,
        choose a convenient payment option, and review your order before confirming. \nWe ensure a secure and smooth checkout for your
        peace of mind. </string>

    <string name="activity_main_descript"> Kick-start your journey by creating an account today! Whether you\'re a customer or seller,
        simply register to unlock a world of possibilities. Unleash the power in seamless world of online computer parts trading right now! </string>

    <string name="banner_heading_one">Save Big with Our App</string>
    <string name="banner_heading_two">Enjoy Doorstep Delivery of Your Purchase</string>
    <string name="banner_heading_three">Checkout Securely, Easily with Our App</string>

    <string name="banner_descript_one">Discover and enjoy the best prices, incredible discounts, offers, deals, and promotions on top brands and categories.</string>
    <string name="banner_descript_two">We offer fast and easy doorstep delivery of your computer items, with free shipping on orders above a certain amount.</string>
    <string name="banner_descript_three">Don’t worry about your payment details or personal information and complete your purchase in just a few clicks.</string>

</resources>